snda.com 2017-12-14

# Shanda Group | Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the website of Shanda Investment Group Limited (“ **Shanda** ,” “ **we** ,” “ **us** ,” or “ **our** ”). We are committed to protecting the privacy and security of visitors to our website (the “ **Site** ”). Please read this privacy policy (the “ **Privacy Policy** ”) carefully to understand generally how we collect personally identifying information about you and how we may use and disclose that personal information.

This Privacy Policy is part of and incorporated into the Terms of Use for the Site (“ **Terms of Use** ”), which govern your use of the Site. Please review the Terms of Use prior to using the Site.

**USE OF OUR SITE OR PROVISION OF ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION CONSTITUTES AGREEMENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITE OR PROVIDE INFORMATION (OR ALLOW OTHERS TO DO SO ON YOUR BEHALF) IF YOU (AND YOUR PRINCIPAL IF YOU ARE ACTING AS AGENT) DO NOT AGREE WITH ALL OF THE TERMS OF USE INCLUDING THIS POLICY.**

****Information Gathering****

We may collect information through your voluntary submission. It is always your choice, or the choice of anyone acting for you, whether to provide personal information, such as name, mailing address, e-mail address or other personally identifying information about yourself (“ **Personal Information** ”). However, in order to obtain certain materials and services from us and to use certain features of the Site, you will need to provide us with Personal Information about yourself, so the decision not to provide this information will limit or eliminate your ability to receive certain materials or use certain features of the Site.

We also use cookies to better understand how our visitors use our Site and to continue to improve it. We may collect the following: your domain name and host for Internet access; the Internet address of the site from which you came; the date and time of your access; your computer’s IP address and information about its operating system, browser and host; the date and time you access the Site and the pages you visit. If you do not want to receive cookies, you may set your browser to reject them. However, if you turn cookies off, you may not have access to some of the Site’s services and features.

****Use and Disclosure of Information****

In general, we use information we collect on the Site to pursue our mission and to engage in the activity for which the information is collected. Specifically, we may use your information to:

  * communicate with you regarding our mission, operations and activities;
  * put you on our mailing list, to the extent you sign up for our newsletter;
  * analyze visitor feedback and track site usage data in order to make improvements to the Site and for other internal purposes;
  * comply with the law or in good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform with the requirements of law or to comply with legal process served on us; and/or
  * undertake other activities in accordance with your consent.

We do not share or otherwise disclose any Personal Information with other organizations except under the following circumstances:

  * to affiliates, staff, partners, contractors, or agents solely for the purpose for which you provided the Personal Information or for any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide Personal Information;
  * to comply with any court order, law or governmental request;
  * in connection with internal or external audit; or
  * in accordance with your consent.

****Change of Privacy Policy****

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change in the future. Your continued use of the Site after we make changes to this Privacy Policy is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check this portion of the Site for any modifications.

****Contact****

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, you can contact us at [contactus@shanda.com](mailto:contactus@shanda.com).

****Effectiveness of the Privacy Policy****

The effective date of this Privacy Policy was October 10, 2016.
